

ALTAMASH ASIF GHORI

Web Developer - Full Stack

About Me

My goal is to become associated with a company where I can utilize my skills and gain further experience while enhancing the company's productivity and reputation. I am able to work both individually and as a member of team. I have great ambitions to succeed in pursuit of my career. I am flexible, reliable and possess excellent time keeping skills



+92-3343801911



altamashasifghori@gmail.com



R-1037 Block 19 F.B Area Karachi Alnoor society Near Power House Shafeeq Modh

Language

- English
- Urdu (basic)

Expertise

- MS Office
- Visual Code Studio
- Logo Creation

Programming Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript (jQuery, Node JS, React JS)
- Python
- MongoDB

Experience

Brookes Pharmaceuticals
Duration: 2023 - 2024

Position: Quality Control Officer - Raw Material Section

 Searle Pharmaceuticals Duration: 2022 - 2023

Position: Quality Control Officer - Stability Section

SGS Pakistan

Duration: 2021 - 2022

Position: Assistant Executive Officer

Bosch Pharmaceuticals

Duration: 2020 - 2021

Position: Quality Assurance Officer - Stability Section

 Bosch Pharmaceuticals Duration: one month.

Position: Internee

Education

University of Karachi

MSc. Applied Chemistry 2020 - 2021

University of Karachi

MSc. Applied Chemistry 2017 - 2019

Certification

Web Development from MBS Computer Collegiate 2020 - 2021

Skills Summary

Design Process

78 %

Project Management

- 81 %